<div xmlns='http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml'>
<!-- Generated by the makeProfilesAndExtensions script -->
<br/><strong>Profiles defined in this guide</strong><br/><br/>
<table class='table table-bordered table-hover table-sm'>
<tr><th>Id</th><th>Url</th><th>Description</th></tr>
<tr>
<td><a href='StructureDefinition-air-agvs-plan-definition.html'>air-agvs-plan-definition</a></td>
<td>https://standards.digital.health.nz/fhir/air/StructureDefinition/air-agvs-plan-definition</td>
<td><p>Defines an immunisation schedule consisting of a series of doses, including custom extensions.</p></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><a href='StructureDefinition-air-careplan.html'>air-careplan</a></td>
<td>https://standards.digital.health.nz/fhir/air/StructureDefinition/air-careplan</td>
<td><p>The FHIR CarePlan resource is used as a structured representation of a consumer’s assigned immunisation schedule, supporting the coordination, tracking, and delivery of vaccinations across various antigen groups. Within the immunisation domain, each CarePlan defines a specific Antigen Group Vaccination (AGV) schedule for an individual and organizes all related vaccination activities into a coherent and accessible format.              In this context, the CarePlan serves as a central framework that brings together planned immunisation events and their corresponding recorded vaccine administrations. Planned events are represented using ImmunizationRecommendation resources, indicating doses that are scheduled based on clinical guidelines and timing. When a vaccine dose is administered, the corresponding Immunization resource is linked back to the relevant planned activity in the CarePlan. This approach ensures that each vaccination event is traceable and that care delivery is aligned with national immunisation protocols.              Each CarePlan acts as a living record of a consumer's immunisation journey for a particular antigen group, capturing past, present, and future planned doses. The activities within the CarePlan are typically ordered by due date, offering a clear and chronological view of the vaccination schedule. This helps healthcare providers monitor compliance, identify overdue or upcoming vaccinations, and coordinate follow-up actions.              Additionally, the CarePlan supports automation and interoperability. When a consumer is onboarded into the immunisation system, relevant AGV schedules are automatically assigned, and CarePlans are created to reflect the full scope of required vaccinations.This profile on the FHIR R4 CarePlan resource adds two extensions from the R5+ CarePlan to more easily represent Immunization and ImmunizationRecommendation links, and to be better aligned with the future direction of FHIR.</p></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><a href='StructureDefinition-air-dose-definition.html'>air-dose-definition</a></td>
<td>https://standards.digital.health.nz/fhir/air/StructureDefinition/air-dose-definition</td>
<td><p>Defines a dose recommendation within an immunisation schedule.</p></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><a href='StructureDefinition-air-immunization-recommendation.html'>air-immunization-recommendation</a></td>
<td>https://standards.digital.health.nz/fhir/air/StructureDefinition/air-immunization-recommendation</td>
<td><p>AIR uses this immunizationRecommendation profile to communicate the details of scheduled events. The specification for this profile is available at https://mohits.atlassian.net/wiki/spaces/NIS/pages/3507781730/AIRImmunizationRecommendation+FHIR+API+into+ImmSOT.</p></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><a href='StructureDefinition-air-immunization.html'>air-immunization</a></td>
<td>https://standards.digital.health.nz/fhir/air/StructureDefinition/air-immunization</td>
<td><p>This is the AIR Immunization Profile, to be used for immunisation records inbound to ImmSoT. It includes a number of constraints designed to enforce ImmSoT&#39;s lean data model approach.</p></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><a href='StructureDefinition-air-location.html'>air-location</a></td>
<td>https://standards.digital.health.nz/fhir/air/StructureDefinition/air-location</td>
<td><p>Ths profile constrains the NZ Location Profile to meet the requirements of AIR as documented at https://mohits.atlassian.net/wiki/spaces/NIS/pages/3445141172/Immunisation+Event+Data+Fields.</p></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><a href='StructureDefinition-air-message-header.html'>air-message-header</a></td>
<td>https://standards.digital.health.nz/fhir/air/StructureDefinition/air-message-header</td>
<td><p>This profile derived from MessageHeader implements extensions to message header required for Immunisation event messaging.</p></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><a href='StructureDefinition-air-patient.html'>air-patient</a></td>
<td>https://standards.digital.health.nz/fhir/air/StructureDefinition/air-patient</td>
<td><p>This profile derived from NZPatient implements the requirements of the Aotearoa Immunisation Register (AIR) Immunisation Source of Truth (ImmSoT).</p></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><a href='StructureDefinition-air-practitioner.html'>air-practitioner</a></td>
<td>https://standards.digital.health.nz/fhir/air/StructureDefinition/air-practitioner</td>
<td><p>This profile derived from NZPractitioner implements the requirements of the Aotearoa Immunisation Register (AIR) Immunisation Source of Truth (ImmSoT).</p></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><a href='StructureDefinition-air-related-person-prf.html'>air-related-person-prf</a></td>
<td>https://standards.digital.health.nz/fhir/air/StructureDefinition/air-related-person-prf</td>
<td><p>This profile of the FHIR R4 RelatedPerson resource includes only the fields used in AIR. The AIR use of this profile specifically includes the use cases covered by the NK1 segment in NIR HL7v2 messaging.</p></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><a href='StructureDefinition-air-serology-report-profile.html'>air-serology-report-profile</a></td>
<td>https://standards.digital.health.nz/fhir/air/StructureDefinition/air-serology-report-profile</td>
<td><p>This profile on the FHIR r4 Observation resource serves to exchange serology report information in support of the legacy NIR data flow that attaches serology info to an existing immunization record and re-sends it. It is cut down substantially from the base Observation resource.</p></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><a href='StructureDefinition-test-air-immunization-recommendation.html'>test-air-immunization-recommendation</a></td>
<td>https://standards.digital.health.nz/fhir/air/StructureDefinition/test-air-immunization-recommendation</td>
<td><p>This profile is for testing the design of the ImmunizationRecommendation profile that will be used to convey information about planned events.</p></td>
</tr>
</table>
</div>